

### **CONTACTS**



Bernhard-Weiß-Str. 1, 10178 Berlin



+4915254837935



sakhr270@gmail.com



https://www.sn-al-absi.com

## **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021

BA Angewandte Informatik

HTW-Berlin

2012 - 2017

BA Wirtschaftsingenieurwesen

TU-Berlin

2011 - 2012

Studienkolleg

Universität des Saarlandes

## **SKILLS**



Java (u.a. Spring boot)



CSS



Django



MvSQ







Reactl

# Languages



Arabic English Deutsch

Berlin, August 2021



Sakhr Nahil Al-ahsi

## **ABOUT ME**

Highly motivated to become an entrepreneur in the near future, I set goals to master Web- and App-development asap. In my free time as well as in the university I have written different projects with Java, Python, Javascript, NodeJS, ReactJS, etc.

Driven and excited to start my coming chapter in Software-Development in a work-environment, I developed my portfolio using Django (see my humble website) to start applying for what I am supposed to be doing in the next 5 years. To be part of your team and contribute in the success of your company as well as of my future will be a huge pleasure of mine. ©

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020 - now

#### IT - 1st & 2nd Level Support

Innocean Worldwide Europe GmbH

With another IT-Working student, we were responsible for the whole IT in the Berlin office, consisted of around 80 employees.

- System-administrative tasks and troubleshooting
- Working with KACE, EasyJob, FortiClient, and Azure
- IT-infrastructure maintenance
- Assistance of all users with any kind of IT-questions and technical difficulties
- Software and Hardware rollouts

2018 - 2020

#### IT Support – 1st Level Support

BMG Rights and Management

This was the second job during my computer science studies. I learned a lot from my team. For example, how to set quality above quantity, to analytically approach an issue, to stay calm under pressure, and to keep tasks structured & in an organized matter in-order not to miss anything.

- Programs I worked with:
  - JIRA, Confluence, Active Directory, Remote Desktop Manager, SilverMonkey, JAMF, and SCCM
- Troubleshooting for different issues.
- Customer Support for colleagues in Berlin as well as from the USA, UK, Spain, Sweden, Holland, France, etc.

2016 - 2017

#### **Customer Support**

Bosch Service Solutions

- Handling of information and emergency calls from automotive customers in Arabic, English and German.
- Receiving and processing of emergency calls & forwarding them to the appropriate rescue coordination center.
- Problem analysis and documentation of customer inquiries.